<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fake call for wednesday addams</string>
    <string name="rateUs">Rate us <small>(AD)</small></string>

    <string-array name="selectCallType">
        <item> Whats App </item>
        <item> Facebook </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="setTimer">
        <item>10 sec</item>
        <item>30 sec</item>
        <item>60 sec</item>
        <item>300 sec</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--Privacy Policy Text-->

    <string name="fragment1">Studio may ask its users to provide necessary identifiable personal information

on using the services to incorporate with other data for improving user’s

experience, which users can turn down any time before proceeding to use the

services. Bear in mind, Straps App Studio does not deliberately offer its

services to the users under the age of 13. So, Straps App Studio urges all of

the users under the age of 13 to seek parental guidance before undertaking the

services. Straps App Studio also advises the parents to monitor and keep a

track of internet activities of their children.\n

By using

the services and products of Straps App Studio, you agree to observe and be

bound by this privacy policy. Straps App Studio has your approval of

collection, processing, use and disclose of the information given by you. You

hereby accept the terms and conditions set by Straps App Studio.

You may

withdraw by not proceeding to using services and products of Straps App Studio.
        <b>\nAccess to Smartphone Features:</b>
<p>Straps App

   Studio may ask its users to allow access to various features of their

   smartphones such as camera, microphone, contacts and location solely for the

   purposes of aligning with the features of our services and products and also to

   increase efficiency and providing influential user experience.</p>

<br />


<br /><br /></string>

    <string name="fragment2"><b>Information Collected by Straps Studio APP:</b>

<p>Users over

   the age of 13 will be asked to register before they will be able to use our

   products and services. Users will have to provide their username, password,

   date of birth and email address. Straps App Studio may attain some non-personal

   data to enhance the user experience on the services and products that it

   provides. Non-personal data may include: browser type, device version, type of

   device and IP address. Please note that this statistical data will solely be

   used to analyse demographical progress. \n This will help Straps App Studio in

   identifying target market and certain areas to focus and bring improvement to. Straps

   App Studio may ask users to provide contact information for surveys and

   communication for future prospects and expectations of users from the

   developers. Statistical data may also include high scores, timings and user

   activities on the services and products to boost up the environment.</p>

<br />
<b>\nSocial Media Connection:</b>
<p>Straps App

   Studio also offers its users to submit their information through any of social

   media platform. Users must be of age 13 to register on these platforms. Straps

   App Studio may obtain data such as name, user ID, gender, location, avatar,

   date of birth and email address. Straps App Studio assures its users that all

   of the necessary gained personal information is encrypted.</p>
<br />


<b>\nUse and disclose of the information collected:</b>
</string>

    <string name="fragment3"><p>Straps App

    Studio collects information only to improve the design of services and products

    to garner more target audience. Straps App Studio ensure its users that all the

    information collected through services or social media platform are fully

    encrypted and are in hashed form through proper channels. Straps App Studio

    takes immense measures to safeguard all the information and prevents from

    unauthorized access.

    However, on

    certain occasions, Straps App Studio may disclose information to third parties

    for advertising purposes. Straps App Studio use ad campaigns and utilities to

    steer its products forward on the market and also for revenue generation

    functions. Users’ information may be collected to tailor the advertisements

    that may interest them.

    Straps App

    Studio may also disclose information to third parties in case if Straps App

    Studio feels there is viable cause to bring a legal action against someone

    deliberately sabotaging services and products.

    Straps App

    Studio also advises the users to take necessary precautions when asked for

    information by third parties which are governed under their policies. Please

    read those policies carefully and then proceed.
     MetaUsage

   We are using Meta service or facebook audience network for face ads running in our product it contains ads or monetization that can help us our business point.

   Here we are showing facebook ads to use.</p>

<br />
<b>\nAmendments to the Privacy Policy:</b>

<p>In order to

   suggest variations, amendments and changes to our current privacy policy, feel

   free to write, email or contact Straps App Studio on the contact information

   provided.</p>

<br /></string>
    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-1204663298278925~3578172412</string>
    <string name="admob_native_large">ca-app-pub-1204663298278925/6598317885</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">884267405897096</string>
    <string name="facebook_client_token">febb297808de6b8fcf3d1fa9547b936f</string>
    <string name="facebook_interstitial_start">1853599031683633_1853599811683555</string>
    <string name="facebook_native_large_start">1853599031683633_1887159208327615</string>
    <string name="facebook_native_large_exit">1853599031683633_1887160174994185</string>
    <string name="facebook_interstitial">1853599031683633_1887160998327436</string>
    <string name="facebook_native_large">1853599031683633_1869360833440786</string>
    <string name="Facebook_Native_placement">1853599031683633_1887160174994185</string>
    <string name="applovin_native_welcome">fd860b513e86c74f</string>
    <string name="applovin_inter_welcome">f7973678cf45f3dd</string>
    <string name="applovin_native">cc0e1f1080336b55</string>
    <string name="applovin_inter">0f79d658b21d0e94</string>
    <string name="applovin_banner">6111afeee9ab69ee</string>
    <string name="applovin_appopen">49f9ca2c19971729</string>
    <!--Real Ids-->
<!--    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-1204663298278925~3578172412</string>-->
<!--    <string name="admob_native_large">ca-app-pub-1204663298278925/6598317885</string>-->

<!--    <string name="facebook_app_id">1853599031683633</string>-->
<!--    <string name="facebook_client_token">febb297808de6b8fcf3d1fa9547b936f</string>-->
<!--    <string name="facebook_interstitial_start">1853599031683633_1853599811683555</string>-->
<!--    <string name="facebook_native_large_start">1853599031683633_1887159208327615</string>-->
<!--    <string name="facebook_native_large_exit">1853599031683633_1887160174994185</string>-->
<!--    <string name="facebook_interstitial">1853599031683633_1887160998327436</string>-->
<!--    <string name="facebook_native_large">1853599031683633_1869360833440786</string>-->
<!--    <string name="Facebook_Native_placement">1853599031683633_1887160174994185</string>-->
<!--    <string name="applovin_native_welcome">fd860b513e86c74f</string>-->
<!--    <string name="applovin_inter_welcome">f7973678cf45f3dd</string>-->
<!--    <string name="applovin_native">cc0e1f1080336b55</string>-->
<!--    <string name="applovin_inter">0f79d658b21d0e94</string>-->
<!--    <string name="applovin_banner">6111afeee9ab69ee</string>-->
<!--    <string name="applovin_appopen">49f9ca2c19971729</string>-->

</resources>